[
  {
    "front": "고무보트",
    "back": "Dinghy"
  },
  {
    "front": "수리하다",
    "back": "Mend"
  },
  {
    "front": "조각",
    "back": "Patch"
  },
  {
    "front": "피크닉",
    "back": "Picnic"
  },
  {
    "front": "강",
    "back": "River"
  },
  {
    "front": "위험한",
    "back": "Dangerous"
  },
  {
    "front": "찾다",
    "back": "Find"
  },
  {
    "front": "좋은",
    "back": "Good"
  },
  {
    "front": "흔들다",
    "back": "Shake"
  },
  {
    "front": "물",
    "back": "Water"
  },
  {
    "front": "바쁘다/분주한",
    "back": "Busy"
  },
  {
    "front": "원하다",
    "back": "Wish"
  },
  {
    "front": "배",
    "back": "Boat"
  },
  {
    "front": "엔진",
    "back": "Engine"
  },
  {
    "front": "조심해",
    "back": "Be careful"
  },
  {
    "front": "오르다",
    "back": "Climb"
  },
  {
    "front": "시간에 맞게",
    "back": "In time"
  },
  {
    "front": "구조하다",
    "back": "Rescue"
  },
  {
    "front": "가족",
    "back": "Family"
  },
  {
    "front": "휴가",
    "back": "Holiday"
  }
]